whatgifs.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy « Best Funny Animated Gifs Updated Every Day – WhatGifs

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

The privacy of the visitors to this website is important to us. Please read this Agreement carefully before using this Website. Your use of this Website constitutes your acceptance to be bound by this Agreement without limitation, qualification or change. If at any time you do not accept all the terms and conditions of this Agreement, you must immediately discontinue use of this Website. We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important to us. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit our network, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. This Agreement sets forth our policies with respect to its operation of this Website.

Please note that you must agree to the Additional Terms used on this website for certain products are services offered as they do carry addional terms associated with them.  In case of a discrepency or inconsistency, the Additional terms will prevail or assume priority.

THIS WEBSITE MAY NOT BE USED FOR ANY REASON OR PURPOSE THAT IS NOT AUTHORIZED IN THIS AGREEMENT. SHOULD YOU FAIL TO COMPLY WITH OUR AGREEMENT AND ADDITIONAL TERMS, WE MAY TERMINATE YOUR ACCESS TO THIS WEBSITE FOR THESE REASONS OR ANY REASONS WE DEEM FIT.

Please note that this website may contain images or text for a mature audience (18+ years old). By accessing this website you are accepting that you are at least 18 years of age.

As well this agreement states, as with most other websites, that we collect and contain the data used in log files (example: IP addresses, ISP provider, what browser is used etc..)  to allow us to personalize and customize our website to better serve you and provide a pleasant experience here and we may share this information with advertisers or third parties that does not disclose your identity or contact information.  

In regards to IP addresses and log files, your IP address may be used to help us diagnoze any problems with website, tracking purposes, analyze patterns or trends so that we may use this information to demographic or aggregate use.

Cookies reside on your computer and help us, and many other websites, collect information about how our website is used, your type of web browser, what version it is therefore we may use this technology to collect information about how you use this website so that we may save and remember registration information or your preferences that you set here to keep track of your visits (example: shopping carts) so that you do not experience the same content once again or need to register on this website once you do so. We use cookies only for this information regarding this policy.

Please note that this website may use web advertising from third parties to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology (Cookies, web beacons etc…) when they advertise with us that provide these advertisers (such as Google AdSense program) with your IP address, ISP name, your browser type and version and more and this is generally used for targeting geographically some advertisements based on your area (USA visitors would receive Google banners for USA only advertisements). Please note you do have the option to disable and selectively turn off our cookies or third party cookies in your browser settings or using Third Party software to do so (Norton Internet Security) but note this may affect yoru ability to interact on this website and other websites you frequent like the inability to login to services and programs should you decide to disable cookies.
